{
    "id": "1c199233683a4d2c86e93590a4b8291a",
    "title": "Much, much of, many, many of",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "4dfc186b70de4954ad153176739fec51",
            "title": "Much, Much Of, Many, Many Of",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "………………….. them are vegetarians.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Many",
                        "Many of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have ………………….. work to do.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "much",
                        "much of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t have ………………….. time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "much",
                        "much of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "There weren’t ………………… students in the class.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "much",
                        "much of",
                        "many",
                        "many of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………….. money has been wasted on this project.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Many",
                        "Much",
                        "Much of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You didn’t eat ……………….. breakfast.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "much",
                        "many",
                        "much of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Not ………………. India is barren.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "much",
                        "many",
                        "much of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "You can’t see ………………… a country in a week.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "much",
                        "many",
                        "much of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "How ………………….. you are going to be there?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "many of",
                        "much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You can have as ……………….. milk as you want.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "much",
                        "much of",
                        "many"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}